<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Roles on Spicy Chicken Quest</title>
    <link>https://www.spicychicken.quest/guides/sproots/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Roles on Spicy Chicken Quest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:06:47 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.spicychicken.quest/guides/sproots/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Everyone</title>
      <link>https://www.spicychicken.quest/guides/sproots/everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:11:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.spicychicken.quest/guides/sproots/everyone/</guid>
      <description>Limit Break is your friend! You can find the action Limit Break in your &amp;ldquo;Actions &amp;amp; Traits&amp;rdquo; window, under &amp;ldquo;General&amp;rdquo;.
 Generally speaking, Limit Break is saved for the last boss for the DPS to use when the boss hits 10% health. This changes as you get further into trials / dungeons / etc. There are unique trials that require the use of LB3 by specific roles in certain circumstances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healers</title>
      <link>https://www.spicychicken.quest/guides/sproots/healers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:11:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.spicychicken.quest/guides/sproots/healers/</guid>
      <description>Healers  Check your party&amp;rsquo;s gear, you&amp;rsquo;ll want to know if they are undergeared for the level dungeon/trial/raid you are doing. Be sure you DPS, future content requires healers to DPS and heal. Get used to it now.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dps</title>
      <link>https://www.spicychicken.quest/guides/sproots/dps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:11:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.spicychicken.quest/guides/sproots/dps/</guid>
      <description>DPS Don&amp;rsquo;t stand in front of the boss It&amp;rsquo;s a good way to get cleaved or tankbusted and die. Dead DPS do no dps.
If you&amp;rsquo;re ranged, stay near healer Healers have heals that are mostly centered around themselves (there are exceptions), but this helps them to be able to do top ups quickly from raidwides. If you decide to stay as far from everyone as possible, do not be surprised if a healer lets you die*</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanks</title>
      <link>https://www.spicychicken.quest/guides/sproots/tanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:11:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.spicychicken.quest/guides/sproots/tanks/</guid>
      <description>Tanks Put on Emnity (threat) Stance Simply having this turned on, you hold threat as long as you hit the targets!
    DRK: Grit WAR: Defiance GNB: Royal Guard PLD: Iron Will            Just because the boss is not physically looking at you does NOT mean you have lost threat There are actions that a boss, or mob will perform that have them physicall turn away from you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
